<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Jonathan de Jesus Portfolio</title>
        <link>https://theonewiththelion.github.io/</link>
        <description>My cool data portfolio site</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><managingEditor>jonathan.dejesus.azor@gmail.com (Jonathan de Jesus Azor)</managingEditor>
            <webMaster>jonathan.dejesus.azor@gmail.com (Jonathan de Jesus Azor)</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2022 11:28:17 -0500</lastBuildDate>
            <atom:link href="https://theonewiththelion.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <item>
    <title>Azure ETL: PowerBI</title>
    <link>https://theonewiththelion.github.io/posts/3post/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2022 11:28:17 -0500</pubDate>
    <author>Jonathan de Jesus</author>
    <guid>https://theonewiththelion.github.io/posts/3post/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[ETL Diagram from Austin API data to PowerBI Idea: Extract data from Austin, separate the information into three different tables, transform the data, upload it to Azure SQL and Visualize the information in PowerBI.
(Insert diagram)
List of Technology used on this project: List of skills used on this project are:
Visual Studio Python - Pandas, SQLAlchemy, Functions(I know, right?) Azure SQL PowerBI Data Modeling (basic) ETL Information: Setup Import Libraries Library from datetime import date, datetime from sqlalchemy import create_engine from sqlalchemy import * import urllib import json import requests import pandas as pd Create connection to database - Azure SQL Library #Azure Server information server = &#39;animalserver.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Basic ETL using Python, Big Query, Data Studio &amp; Airflow</title>
    <link>https://theonewiththelion.github.io/posts/second_post/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 23:20:46 -0500</pubDate>
    <author>Jonathan de Jesus</author>
    <guid>https://theonewiththelion.github.io/posts/second_post/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[ETL Diagram of my first project Idea: Get data raw data from Austin Crime, transform it, store the data in the cloud and utilize a visualization too to properly present the data.
List of Technology used in this project are: Visual Studio Python Pandas Big Query Data Studio Airflow 1. Library Imports 2. Extraction: API containing the crime data from Austin, Texas. 3. Transformation: Used Visual Studio &amp; Pandas. Transformation: Rename of Columns Transformation: Change format of &ldquo;Date Ocurred&rdquo; from military time, to standard time Transformation: Change format of &ldquo;Date Reported&rdquo; from military time, to standard time 4.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Do you want to set an awesome website like this ?</title>
    <link>https://theonewiththelion.github.io/posts/first_post/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 20:34:07 -0500</pubDate>
    <author>Jonathan de Jesus Azor</author>
    <guid>https://theonewiththelion.github.io/posts/first_post/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[If you want to setup/host/deploy a website on GitHub please check: Ivy&rsquo;s blog.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
