<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>All Posts - Jonathan de Jesus Portfolio</title>
        <link>https://theonewiththelion.github.io/posts/</link>
        <description>All Posts | Jonathan de Jesus Portfolio</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><managingEditor>jonathan.dejesus.azor@gmail.com (Jonathan de Jesus Azor)</managingEditor>
            <webMaster>jonathan.dejesus.azor@gmail.com (Jonathan de Jesus Azor)</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2022 11:28:17 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://theonewiththelion.github.io/posts/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Azure ETL: PowerBI - Coming Soon/Work in Progress - Screenshots pending</title>
    <link>https://theonewiththelion.github.io/posts/3post/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2022 11:28:17 -0500</pubDate>
    <author>Jonathan de Jesus</author>
    <guid>https://theonewiththelion.github.io/posts/3post/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[ETL Diagram from Austin API data to PowerBI Idea: Extract data from Austin, separate the information into three different tables, transform the data, upload it to Azure SQL and Visualize the information in PowerBI. (Insert diagram)
List of Technology used on this project: List of skills used in this project are:
Visual Studio Python - Pandas, SQLAlchemy, Functions(I know, right?) Azure SQL PowerBI Data Modeling ETL Information: Extraction Import Libraries from datetime import date, datetime from sqlalchemy import create_engine from sqlalchemy import Table, Column, Integer, String, MetaData, DateTime, Float import urllib import json import requests import pandas as pd Create connection to Database Extract data from API Create 3 tables in Azure SQL Store data in 3 different tables: names, dates, outcome Transformation: Extract information from tables - Azure SQL Transform column monthyear, split values into two new columns Transform column date, split information into 3 new columns Transform column date of birth, take the information on the left of “T” delete columns: Date time, month year Load values into the table dates: since is tjhe only table where I performed transformation Load: pending Created 3 new table (Production simulation) Load records into new tables Visualization: Will be using PowerBI ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Basic ETL using Python, Big Query, Data Studio &amp; Airflow</title>
    <link>https://theonewiththelion.github.io/posts/second_post/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 23:20:46 -0500</pubDate>
    <author>Jonathan de Jesus</author>
    <guid>https://theonewiththelion.github.io/posts/second_post/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[ETL Diagram of my first project Idea: Get data raw data from Austin Crime, transform it, store the data in the cloud and utilize a visualization too to properly present the data.
List of Technology used in this project are: Visual Studio Python Pandas Big Query Data Studio Airflow 1. Library Imports 2. Extraction: API containing the crime data from Austin, Texas. 3. Transformation: Used Visual Studio &amp; Pandas. Transformation: Rename of Columns Transformation: Change format of &ldquo;Date Ocurred&rdquo; from military time, to standard time Transformation: Change format of &ldquo;Date Reported&rdquo; from military time, to standard time 4.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Do you want to set an awesome website like this ?</title>
    <link>https://theonewiththelion.github.io/posts/first_post/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 20:34:07 -0500</pubDate>
    <author>Jonathan de Jesus Azor</author>
    <guid>https://theonewiththelion.github.io/posts/first_post/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[If you want to setup/host/deploy a website on GitHub please check: Ivy&rsquo;s blog.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
